+801-503-2036



aubrey_jones07@hotmail.com



https://aubrey-jones-web-development-portfolio.netlify.app/



https://aubrey-jones-ux-uiportfolio.netlify.app/

Riverton, Utah 💰

Aubrey JONES

UX/UI Designer && Developer

My name is Aubrey Jones and I often daydream, learn, execute, and teach UX/UI design and frontend web development. I am always ready for a challenge that helps customers have a better user experience through the latest technologies in UX/UI design and frontend web development. Feel free to connect.

SKILLS

UX & UI Design

Interviews, User Personas, Affinity
Diagrams, Empathy Maps, User Journey
Maps, Sketches, Wireframing, Unit Testing,
Style Guides, Design Systems, A/B Testing,
Prototyping
Figma, Adobe XD, Sketch

FRONT-END Development

HTML/CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Material UI5 JavaScript, React JS

BACK-END Development

MongoDB, Express.JS, Node.JS

EDUCATION

Utah Valley University 2017 – 2021 Bachelor's Degree

Web Design and Development
Emphasis in Web and App Development

DevMountain 2016 - 2016

Certificate

UX/UI Design

Salt Lake Community College 2011 - 2016

Associate's Degree

General Studies

EXPERIENCE

O1. UX/UI Designer Instructional Specialist - Tutor - Grader Trilogy Educational Services - edX Bootcamps

November 2020 - Current

As a UX/UI Designer Instructional Specialist I get to mentor students and guide them throughout the UX/UI design thinking process and front-end web development. I provide written and verbal feedback on presented projects.

02. UX/UI Designer Codafi Technologies

September 2020 - November 2020

May 2018 - December 2020

We worked on design sprints as a team which included research, definition and ideation, wireframing, prototyping, and testing. We communicated with the client and designed and updated their style guide and feature requests.

03. UX/UI Designer and Developer Intern The Family Literacy Centers

I worked on design sprints which included research, definition and ideation, wireframing, prototyping, and testing. I redesigned their Algebra I program to have a modern layout and updated it to fit HTML5 and CSS requirements.